This section, mostly we are concentrating in network based attacks that will be commonly
used by the detectors to down the servos and do some other kind of attacks, like sniffing
and all, so monitoring the user name's passwords in the network, so we will see briefly
how the attackers will do the attacks one by one, first of all, we will discuss about
the denial of service, the Dorset attacks, so let me open the canva and we will draw something
and we will learn about the Dorset attacks, so let me take this is the web server, so
let us think, it's not a high performance web server, only this web server can be able
to handle only the 1000 reduced at a time, so now many machines like the 1000 machines,
1,000 accessing this web server, or do anything, take anything watch movies or downloading
the uploading pictures, etc etc, and all, if anyone of the other users, 1000 and
1, if he tries to login, this web server can't able to provide service to this user because
it can only handle only 1000 reduced at a time, so in the task attack, what the attacker
will do, they will create a, they will send multiple request to the web server simultaneously
within a few seconds, so now the server can't able to handle any of their request, so
it will be shut down, so it will not give any results to anyone of them, okay, for an
example, so let's take a human behavior, so if someone asks me, like how are you, why
will say I am fine, so if two of them are coming and they are asking which food they are
eating, and where you went, yesterday, so even I can able to answer within a few seconds
answering one by one, if 10 people simultaneously asking what you did the rest of the
day, so it's like an investigation, some police investigation phone, at that time I was
unable to answer all the questions because it will be confusing for me, my mind will be
frustrated, so I can't able to provide answers to everyone, so the same, the server will
be thinking, okay, a lot of requests are coming, and I was unable to answer any of them,
so it will be in a shut down state, it will go to the shut down state, okay, so once
it gets shut down, so the administrator need to restart the service, and again they need
to start the server, okay, we can do the dasa tag in our column machine, we have a lot
of tools for doing the dasa tag, so don't worry about that, we will see in practical,
so before that we will see the distributor denial of service, okay, so in dasa tag in dasa,
so one computer it will send a n number of requests, okay, infinity number of requests used
to the server, so the server will be shut down, so infinity number of requests used to the
server, so the server will be unable to handle all the requests or the time, so it will
be in a shut down, in the dasa tag there will be not one system, there will be a lot
of machines, like n number of machines, it will send the request simultaneously to the
web server, okay, so now the web server will be completely down, okay, this is the exact
scenario, what will happen in dasa and dasa tag, so say discuss, we have a lot of tools
to do that, the dasa tag is like a distributor denial of service, in the name we can understand,
so distributed, we have a distributed computer, so we are using that computer and doing
that, doing such a tags, so let's take a practical example here, so we have two machines
and two or Kali, just note the one calling machine is 20, 24 point third version, the other
Kali machine is 20, 24 point second versions, so what I am going to do, I am doing, I am
going to do a dasa tag from 20, 24 point two to 20, 24 point three, okay, from that machine
to this machine, okay, so if you see my IP, the IP was 18.3, so I just chartered the Apache
to server in Kali Linux, so I already said, if there is a website, we can target that website
and we can do our dasa tag, so now let's see my server IP will be, I am considering this
machine as a web server and this is the attack term machine, 24.2, this is an attack
term machine, okay, and now you can see the Apache was loading, there is a one web server
was running and we have a lot of tools to do the DOS, so I was using a DDoS attack
tool, so no worry, you can download that from GitHub, so here you can find an N number
of tools for doing the DOS and DDoS attack, so whichever tools you are comfortable with,
you can go for that tool and you can do the DOS, okay, so this is a good tool which I am
using, so let's think of it, let's go inside the directory and let's check what was there,
so DDoS attack.py and let's start the Python, so now you can see, when I start the
executor the DDoS.py, it was asking for a target IP, we know we are going to group 4, sorry,
we are going to do a DDoS attack for this service 192.6.18.3 and we need to search the target
of port, so we can use just 84.43 whatever you can, you can set that, okay, before that
let me start a wire shock here to monitor what's happening in our network, so let's start
the wire shock here also, in both of the machine, so we can easily monitor what, what
electricity speed was receiving, okay, so now the oil shock was started and let me close
other tabs, I will post this also, let's start this and let's start this, so currently
there is no like used, so let's do a DDoS, so the attack was going to start, it's a 50
days now and 75% days, so now see once the attack gets started, so you can see a large number
of executors coming from 192.16.18.27, so in this machine, so you can in 24.2 machine, you
can easily find out, so in the source IP sending some rectus to the destination, it's a
huge number of rectus, let's stop this, so within a few seconds you can see, there's
a 81,000 something packets were sent to different different ports, 14.3, 79 and different
different ports, so now you can see a lot and a lot of rectus was coming up with enough
few seconds, it was coming from 18.27 IP and it was receiving to 18.3 IP, so now you can
understand, so there is a lot of rectus targeting this server and it was giving some
rectus, so this server can't able to handle this rectus and the server will be easily shut
up, it will take some time to completely get down this server, okay, so now you can find
it, the source IP and the source Mac destination Mac, so it's a dummy, it looks like a dummy
packet, something will be inside this packet, okay, so this is the explanation for a DOS and
DRAS attack, we have seen this in practical how to do, do this, so if you have a lab you
can also try to do this task and you can understand what will come here and you can also
you can investigate through OSHA, okay, so let's hop of this video and we will continue
our network based attack in our next video. Thank you, bye bye.